[Music]
[Applause]
so what is your name my name is nid rad
and where are we right now we're here at
the world famous Global headquarters of
manual life in Toronto can you show me
around let's do
it so I heard you're on a baseball
fantasy team with I grew up in Montreal
uh the suburbs of Montreal and sort of
an immigrant household um I would say I
was sort of stuck out I was a bit
different thinking back though I I
actually built up a lot of resiliency
going through that I was lucky because I
found my passion right away I know a lot
of people take take some time to find
their passion I I found my passion right
away I had such a good experience there
and it set me up for Success that I
wanted to give back to the university so
I set up about 10 years ago a uh bursary
an entry bursary for high achieving
actual incoming actual mathematics
students with financial need and there's
actually nothing as rewarding to say uh
to hear uh that that uh bur series made
a significant difference in their uh
their lives and their careers I read
that you're naturally an introvert how
has that impacted your career I am
definitely an introvert when I was in
Singapore I had to go on the stage in
front of a thousand plus insurance
agents and motivate them ra to sell life
insurance to sell manual life life
insurance product that was totally
outside my comfort zone and I remember
the first time I did that I think I
struggled a little bit with that I got
feedback I tried to improve I kept going
back and doing it again and again uh and
I think I've got okay at it as a leader
you have to be humble you have to
realize that you don't have all the
answers uh I've seen leaders come in and
think they know everything and not
listen um I think it's really important
that you get different perspectives you
listen you evaluate um and you come to
an optimal
[Music]
decision take a look at Sports and your
own passion for basketball baseball and
some of the sports we've talked about a
lot of people who are sort of in that
space are very competitive winning is on
their mind so how do you take that
winning culture and apply that to manual
life well we we want to win here at man
life right we're we're in a competitive
space um in the insurance industry
throughout the globe um especially in
Canada uh the idea that I I'd like to do
in Canada is to take manual life to
another level how to differentiate
yourselves how to win in the market so
it's manual life and the rest when you
think of the insurance industry in
Canada so n why did you choose to work
at manual life I started in man life in
1995 so we're going we're going PR
pretty far back I remember thinking I
want to work for a large Canadian
successful Canadian company a global uh
brand um it's really exciting to be a
part of a company that is here for the
long run what do you want your legacy at
manual life to be I've talked about
winning a lot um and manual life is one
of the bigger insurance companies in in
Canada we've got a nice uh market share
uh I don't want to be known as one of
the biggest biggest insurance companies
in Canada I want to be known as uh the
insurance industry in Canada is made up
of manual life and the rest and that's
how I'd like to go up
[Music]